[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Eva, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Eva", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I'm good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "Lovely to have you in my studio.", "answer_tokens": ["Lovely", "to", "have", "you", "in", "my", "studio", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Occupation.", "answer_tokens": ["Occupation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What do you call yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "call", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Actor is on there.", "answer_tokens": ["Actor", "is", "on", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "That excites me?", "question_tokens": ["That", "excites", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Yes, one of those things that I mentioned.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "one", "of", "those", "things", "that", "I", "mentioned", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I mean like when you're older you have a better appreciation for history or for knowledge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "like", "when", "you", "'re", "older", "you", "have", "a", "better", "appreciation", "for", "history", "or", "for", "knowledge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "What are you -- what are you actually studying?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "--", "what", "are", "you", "actually", "studying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Chicano studies and political science.", "answer_tokens": ["Chicano", "studies", "and", "political", "science", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "What is Chicano studies?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "Chicano", "studies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Chicano studies is the study mostly of the Mexican- American movement that has happened in the United States, and the history of Mexican-Americans.", "answer_tokens": ["Chicano", "studies", "is", "the", "study", "mostly", "of", "the", "Mexican-", "American", "movement", "that", "has", "happened", "in", "the", "United", "States", ",", "and", "the", "history", "of", "Mexican-Americans", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 73, "question": "Can I?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "I", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 74, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "You can be an honorary Chicano?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "an", "honorary", "Chicano", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "You can be an honorary Chicano.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "be", "an", "honorary", "Chicano", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "What do I have to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "I", "have", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well, you have to help us in the fight for social justice and believe in equality for everyone.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", "help", "us", "in", "the", "fight", "for", "social", "justice", "and", "believe", "in", "equality", "for", "everyone", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "How important are your roots to you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "are", "your", "roots", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Pretty important.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "important", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "You had to learn Spanish?", "question_tokens": ["You", "had", "to", "learn", "Spanish", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Do you speak French?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "speak", "French", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I speak a bit of French.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "speak", "a", "bit", "of", "French", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "Immigration?", "question_tokens": ["Immigration", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "When I came here, I couldn't believe the hot issue it really is.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "came", "here", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "believe", "the", "hot", "issue", "it", "really", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "How would you fix things?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "fix", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, that's a loaded question.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "loaded", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Do you think he has lived up to expectations?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "has", "lived", "up", "to", "expectations", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "I think he had a lot on his plate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "had", "a", "lot", "on", "his", "plate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "It's heartbreaking to see kids having to do this in modern ages, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "heartbreaking", "to", "see", "kids", "having", "to", "do", "this", "in", "modern", "ages", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "The great thing about this documentary is that -- actually we produced it so it can be used as a political tool to change the way agricultural workers are treated in the United States.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "great", "thing", "about", "this", "documentary", "is", "that", "--", "actually", "we", "produced", "it", "so", "it", "can", "be", "used", "as", "a", "political", "tool", "to", "change", "the", "way", "agricultural", "workers", "are", "treated", "in", "the", "United", "States", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "You're quite an activist, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "quite", "an", "activist", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Yes?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "You shouldn't be, but I am.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "should", "n't", "be", ",", "but", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "How do you deal with that as someone who's got in your own family?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "deal", "with", "that", "as", "someone", "who", "'s", "got", "in", "your", "own", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "How is she doing?", "question_tokens": ["How", "is", "she", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "She's doing amazing.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "doing", "amazing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "I mean, to have somebody in your life who, none of that means anything to at all and who's not impressed by any of that because why would she be?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "to", "have", "somebody", "in", "your", "life", "who", ",", "none", "of", "that", "means", "anything", "to", "at", "all", "and", "who", "'s", "not", "impressed", "by", "any", "of", "that", "because", "why", "would", "she", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", ",", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "It makes it very natural for you, doesn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "makes", "it", "very", "natural", "for", "you", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "She's very grounding.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "very", "grounding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "Don't you find that a bit unsettling when you go home?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "find", "that", "a", "bit", "unsettling", "when", "you", "go", "home", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 306, "question": "No entourage?", "question_tokens": ["No", "entourage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "matter", "with", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I'm really not a complainer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "really", "not", "a", "complainer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Do we say slouch, lay back, think of England?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "say", "slouch", ",", "lay", "back", ",", "think", "of", "England", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I'm going to go sit in your lap.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "go", "sit", "in", "your", "lap", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Why do you think I put you in an uncomfortable chair?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "think", "I", "put", "you", "in", "an", "uncomfortable", "chair", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Yes, I tweet a lot.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "tweet", "a", "lot", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Demi Moore", "Ashton"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "What's the attraction of Twitter?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "attraction", "of", "Twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "You know it's funny because Demi Moore and Ashton were, like, you know, the really pioneers of getting everybody on Twitter.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "it", "'s", "funny", "because", "Demi", "Moore", "and", "Ashton", "were", ",", "like", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "really", "pioneers", "of", "getting", "everybody", "on", "Twitter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Are you a drunk tweeter?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "drunk", "tweeter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "No, not drunk tweeting.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "drunk", "tweeting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "It's more to do with putting stuff out there where you -- why did I do that?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "more", "to", "do", "with", "putting", "stuff", "out", "there", "where", "you", "--", "why", "did", "I", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "EX", "WRB", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Like if you choose to make your life so public?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "if", "you", "choose", "to", "make", "your", "life", "so", "public", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Because it's so easy now to become a celebrity?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "it", "'s", "so", "easy", "now", "to", "become", "a", "celebrity", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "No, because I mean -- really I don't really care.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "because", "I", "mean", "--", "really", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "You're look like a mini Oprah, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "look", "like", "a", "mini", "Oprah", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Oprah"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What's the Eva Longoria brand?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "Eva", "Longoria", "brand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Well, I think similar to Oprah.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "similar", "to", "Oprah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eva Longoria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Are you tough enough to be a mogul, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "tough", "enough", "to", "be", "a", "mogul", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Are you not to be messed with?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "not", "to", "be", "messed", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I am not to be messed with.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "not", "to", "be", "messed", "with", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "I mean seriously, could you ever go out with a man with a soft handshake?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "seriously", ",", "could", "you", "ever", "go", "out", "with", "a", "man", "with", "a", "soft", "handshake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Never.", "answer_tokens": ["Never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Who?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I'm not going to name them now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "name", "them", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "Who taught you direct eye contact and firm handshake?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "taught", "you", "direct", "eye", "contact", "and", "firm", "handshake", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Probably my family.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "my", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "They're all strong women, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "all", "strong", "women", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "And they're all strong, strong women.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "they", "'re", "all", "strong", ",", "strong", "women", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "What do they make -- what do they make of what's happened to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "make", "--", "what", "do", "they", "make", "of", "what", "'s", "happened", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "They're proud.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Are they -- do they quite believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "--", "do", "they", "quite", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "Well, I was always different.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "always", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Do I like being famous?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "I", "like", "being", "famous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Or does it make no difference?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "does", "it", "make", "no", "difference", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Did you imagine you would be married for life?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "imagine", "you", "would", "be", "married", "for", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "But did you really believe this was the guy, this was the one for you for life?", "question_tokens": ["But", "did", "you", "really", "believe", "this", "was", "the", "guy", ",", "this", "was", "the", "one", "for", "you", "for", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBD", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "It all came out.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "all", "came", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "The marriage?", "question_tokens": ["The", "marriage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Do you feel humiliated?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "humiliated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "A bit, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "bit", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What more could a guy want, frankly?", "question_tokens": ["What", "more", "could", "a", "guy", "want", ",", "frankly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJR", "MD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, you know, like I said, we just -- you want different things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "like", "I", "said", ",", "we", "just", "--", "you", "want", "different", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Is there any way back as far as you're concerned, if a man behaves that way towards you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "way", "back", "as", "far", "as", "you", "'re", "concerned", ",", "if", "a", "man", "behaves", "that", "way", "towards", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Do you think he wants to?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "wants", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 614, "question": "Would you get married again?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "get", "married", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 615, "answer": "Oh, that's a horrible question to ask when I just got divorced.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "horrible", "question", "to", "ask", "when", "I", "just", "got", "divorced", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "It's not top of your list, is it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "top", "of", "your", "list", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "Are you actually divorced yet?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "actually", "divorced", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Yes, we've been divorced for a while.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "'ve", "been", "divorced", "for", "a", "while", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "How old is your wife?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "is", "your", "wife", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "She's 10 years younger than me.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "10", "years", "younger", "than", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I recommend it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "recommend", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", ":"], "qSentId": 647, "question": "I mean, even though she's younger?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "even", "though", "she", "'s", "younger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Tell me about your --", "answer_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "your", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Do you mind when those pictures come out?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "mind", "when", "those", "pictures", "come", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Do you like being in love?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "being", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "I love being in love.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "being", "in", "love", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "properly", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Once.", "answer_tokens": ["Once", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "And you married him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "married", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "And I married him.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "I", "married", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "How many times have you been in love?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "been", "in", "love", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "More than that.", "answer_tokens": ["More", "than", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "What's the next subject?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "next", "subject", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Well, you did say move on, but I think we'll stick around for a while if you don't mind.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "did", "say", "move", "on", ",", "but", "I", "think", "we", "'ll", "stick", "around", "for", "a", "while", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", ":", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "Has what happened to you damaged your ability to love, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "what", "happened", "to", "you", "damaged", "your", "ability", "to", "love", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "You know, I thought it would -- was actually really, was really disappointed in the concept of loyalty and faithfulness and things like that, but, no, I can't let it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "thought", "it", "would", "--", "was", "actually", "really", ",", "was", "really", "disappointed", "in", "the", "concept", "of", "loyalty", "and", "faithfulness", "and", "things", "like", "that", ",", "but", ",", "no", ",", "I", "ca", "n't", "let", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "What is the way to have a civilized break?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "way", "to", "have", "a", "civilized", "break", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 736, "question": "Did that particularly worry you, that you kind of reached a point in a relationship where you were about to have children and suddenly it's not the future you thought you had?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "that", "particularly", "worry", "you", ",", "that", "you", "kind", "of", "reached", "a", "point", "in", "a", "relationship", "where", "you", "were", "about", "to", "have", "children", "and", "suddenly", "it", "'s", "not", "the", "future", "you", "thought", "you", "had", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 737, "answer": "It's still my future, I still will have children.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "still", "my", "future", ",", "I", "still", "will", "have", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 745, "question": "I mean, are you in an exclusive situation with your playboy or is there a door opening here?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "are", "you", "in", "an", "exclusive", "situation", "with", "your", "playboy", "or", "is", "there", "a", "door", "opening", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 746, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 758, "question": "If you had a dream number, what it would be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "a", "dream", "number", ",", "what", "it", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 759, "answer": "It would be four.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "four", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 783, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 784, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 812, "question": "Why should I get excited by your cookbook?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "I", "get", "excited", "by", "your", "cookbook", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 813, "answer": "I love to cook.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "to", "cook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 824, "question": "Oh, it's called guac, is it, you call in the trade?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "called", "guac", ",", "is", "it", ",", "you", "call", "in", "the", "trade", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 825, "answer": "Well, guacamole.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "guacamole", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Now, are these your little signature things?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "are", "these", "your", "little", "signature", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "These are my signature things.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "are", "my", "signature", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 852, "question": "Now the interview starts, huh?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "the", "interview", "starts", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 853, "answer": "I love margaritas.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "margaritas", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 856, "question": "But this is all quite simple food, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "this", "is", "all", "quite", "simple", "food", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 857, "answer": "It's all very simple and, you know, I'm not a chef.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "all", "very", "simple", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "a", "chef", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "Do you think there's someone watching this who can't cook, like me, if they read this book?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "there", "'s", "someone", "watching", "this", "who", "ca", "n't", "cook", ",", "like", "me", ",", "if", "they", "read", "this", "book", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "WP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "If you can read, you can cook.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "can", "read", ",", "you", "can", "cook", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 894, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 895, "answer": "You know, the people you reach.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "people", "you", "reach", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 901, "question": "Oh, God, what are you going to say?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "God", ",", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 902, "answer": "Sex.", "answer_tokens": ["Sex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 914, "question": "Did she tell you that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "tell", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 915, "answer": "She told me that.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "told", "me", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 916, "question": "On air?", "question_tokens": ["On", "air", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 917, "answer": "No, it wasn't on air, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "n't", "on", "air", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 923, "question": "None?", "question_tokens": ["None", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 924, "answer": "Good for Gwyn.", "answer_tokens": ["Good", "for", "Gwyn", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 930, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 931, "answer": "I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 938, "question": "When you see the Oscars on TV, do you think -- do you start practicing the speech that may never happen?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "the", "Oscars", "on", "TV", ",", "do", "you", "think", "--", "do", "you", "start", "practicing", "the", "speech", "that", "may", "never", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 939, "answer": "No, I don't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 945, "question": "Do you like politics?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 946, "answer": "I actually love --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "actually", "love", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 961, "question": "Can you imagine?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "imagine", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 962, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 965, "question": "What about Oprah-Eva ticket?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Oprah-Eva", "ticket", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 966, "answer": "ONGORIA: I know.", "answer_tokens": ["ONGORIA", ":", "I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 971, "question": "What's been the moment you'd relive tomorrow if you had the chance?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "moment", "you", "'d", "relive", "tomorrow", "if", "you", "had", "the", "chance", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 972, "answer": "You know, people ask me this all the time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "people", "ask", "me", "this", "all", "the", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Andy Garcia"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 990, "question": "Any movies?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 991, "answer": "Well, yes, I just did -- finished a film called \"Cristiada\" with Andy Garcia.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "just", "did", "--", "finished", "a", "film", "called", "``", "Cristiada", "''", "with", "Andy", "Garcia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["fall"]}, "docId": "110723pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 996, "question": "When's it out?", "question_tokens": ["When", "'s", "it", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 997, "answer": "In the fall.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "the", "fall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]